<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Quotes xmlns="https://github.com/einajade-forest/WW-Quotes" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://github.com/einajade-forest/WW-Quotes Quotes.xsd">
  <Quote Id="1">
    <Text>Marriage lets you annoy one special person for the rest of your life.</Text>
    <Source>Unknown</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="2">
    <Text>Marriage is not just spiritual communion, it is also remembering to take out the trash.</Text>
    <Source>Joyce Brothers</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="3">
    <Text>The great marriages are partnerships. It can’t be a great marriage without being a partnership.</Text>
    <Source>Helen Mirren</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="4">
    <Text>A successful marriage requires falling in love many times, always with the same person.</Text>
    <Source>Mignon McLaughlin</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="5">
    <Text>So it’s not gonna be easy. It’s going to be really hard; we’re gonna have to work at this everyday, but I want to do that because I want you. I want all of you, forever, everyday. You and me… everyday.</Text>
    <Source>Nicholas Sparks, The Notebook</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="6">
    <Text>May this marriage be full of laughter, our every day in paradise.</Text>
    <Source>Rumi</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="7">
    <Text>A happy marriage is a long conversation which always seems too short.</Text>
    <Source>Andre Maurois</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="8">
    <Text>All that I ever wanted was to just hear music, and when I met you, I heard you. And, Rachel, you're the most beautiful thing I've ever heard. Thank you for marrying me.</Text>
    <Source>Sidney Williams, Rachel Getting Married</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="9">
    <Text>I have a love in my life. It makes me stronger than anything you can imagine.</Text>
    <Source>Barry Egan, Punch-Drunk Love</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="10">
    <Text>It was a million tiny little things that, when you added them all up, they meant we were supposed to be together, and I knew it. I knew it the very first time I touched her. It was like coming home, only to no home I'd ever known. I was just taking her hand to help her out of a car and I knew. It was like magic.</Text>
    <Source>Sam Baldwin, Sleepless in Seattle</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="11">
    <Text>He stepped down, trying not to look long at her, as if she were the sun, yet he saw her, like the sun, even without looking.</Text>
    <Source>Leo Tolstoy, Anna Karenina</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="12">
    <Text>It doesn’t matter if the guy is perfect or the girl is perfect, as long as they are perfect for each other.</Text>
    <Source>Robin Williams, Good Will Hunting</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="13">
    <Text>In my opinion, the best thing you can do is find someone who loves you for exactly what you are. Good mood, bad mood, ugly, pretty, handsome, what have you.</Text>
    <Source>Mac MacGuff, Juno</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="14">
    <Text>So how does it happen, great love? Nobody knows… but what I can tell you is that it happens in the blink of an eye. One moment you’re enjoying your life, and the next you’re wondering how you ever lived without them.</Text>
    <Source>Hitch, Hitch</Source>
  </Quote>
  <Quote Id="15">
    <Text>It could have happened lots of ways. But this is the way it happened. This is the path we took. This is our story.</Text>
    <Source>Jenny Han, P.S. I Still Love You</Source>
  </Quote>
</Quotes>